export const data=[
    {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
        ans:1,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:4,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:2,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
        ans:1,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:4,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:2,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
        ans:1,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:4,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:2,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
        ans:1,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:4,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:2,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:3,
    },
        {
        question:"wich device is required for the internet connection?",
        option1:"Modem",
        option2:"Router",
        option3:"LAN",
        option4:"WAN",
         ans:1,
    },
    
]